And the answer to the first question is No.
最初の問題の答えは NO です
The first step before running A* is defining
A* を実行する前の最初のステップは
a discrete set of states that represent the world we want to plan in.
これらかプランニングする世界を表す離散的な状態を定義することです
Before we say A* is a discrete method.
その前に A* とは離散メソッドのことです
For the second question, the answer is yes.
2 問目の答えは YES です
In order to be a valid,
有効にするためには
A* heuristic have to be optimistic.
A* ヒューリスティックを最適化する必要があります
Meaning that they should underestimate the actual cost to go from the cell to the goal.
セルからゴールまでの実際のコストより低く見積もる必要があります
A* does always find the solution if one exists.
A* は解があれば必ず見つけます
Which as you recall meaning that A* is a complete planning algorithm.
A*は完全な計画アルゴリズムであることを思い出してください
So, the next assertion is somewhat tricky
次の表明は少し複雑です
because it depends on the search space that is being used and what it represents.
これは使用するサーチスペースとそれが表現するものに左右されるためです
If the search space represent only the position x,y like you saw in the previous examples,
前の例でご覧になったようにサーチスペースが
and we're trying to move a car,
車を動かそうとしている場合
there is no guarantees that the sequence of position returned by A* will be drivable.
A* によって返される位置のシーケンスが実行可能か保証がありません
Therefore, the answer to this question is no.
したがって この問題の答えは NO です
However, remember that A* is the graph search algorithm.
一方で A* はグラフサーチアルゴリズムであることを覚えておいてください
We can define a more complex search space including heading
見出しを含めた、より複雑な検索スペースを定義できる
for example and restrict connections between cells such
セルを閉じた時に上に追加した
that when we close a cell we add to the up and set only cells
セル間のコネクションを制限し クロージングセルから新しいセルまで遷移する
such that the transition from the closing cell to the new cells are drivable.
セルのみを設定することが可能です
If we do that the resulting path will be drivable as well.
このような場合も リザルトパスは実行可能です
This corresponds to running A* on a lattice.
これは文字列上での実行 A* に対応します
Now the last question.
それでは 最後の質問です
It is true that the solution A* finds are always
ソリューション A* は入力に使用した環境の離散化を考慮して
optimal with respect to the discretization of the environment that was used as an input.
必ず最適な状態を探します
The more granular the discretization,
離散化の粒度が細かいほど
the better the solution.
よりよいソリューションとなります
We call this resolution optimal.
これを解像度最適といいます